[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the keyword for determine the constant value at Javascript ?",
    "answer1": "let",
    "answer2": "var",
    "answer3": "object",
    "answer4": "const",
    "correctAnswer": "answer4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error ?",
    "answer1": "Syntax error",
    "answer2": "Missing of semicolons",
    "answer3": "Division by zero",
    "answer4": "Missing of bracket",
    "correctAnswer": "answer2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following function of the String object returns the character in the string starting at the specified position via the specified number of characters ?",
    "answer1": "slice()",
    "answer2": "split()",
    "answer3": "substr()",
    "answer4": "search()",
    "correctAnswer": "answer3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that :",
    "answer1": "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
    "answer2": "Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
    "answer3": "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
    "answer4": "Both are not same at all.",
    "correctAnswer": "answer3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that :",
    "answer1": "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
    "answer2": "Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
    "answer3": "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
    "answer4": "Both are not same at all.",
    "correctAnswer": "answer3"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which one of the following is an ternary operator ? ",
    "answer1": "?",
    "answer2": ":",
    "answer3": "-",
    "answer4": "+",
    "correctAnswer": "answer1"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "'An expression that can legally appear on the left side of an assignment expression.' is a well known explanation for variables, properties of objects, and elements of arrays. They are called : ",
    "answer1": "Properties",
    "answer2": "Prototypes",
    "answer3": "Definition",
    "answer4": "Lvalue",
    "correctAnswer": "answer4"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "In a case, where the value of the operator is NULL , the typeof returned by the unary operator is called : ",
    "answer1": "object",
    "answer2": "string",
    "answer3": "boolean",
    "answer4": "undefined",
    "correctAnswer": "answer1"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "A collection of elements of the same data type which may either in order or not, is called : ",
    "answer1": "String",
    "answer2": "Array",
    "answer3": "Serialized Object",
    "answer4": "Object",
    "correctAnswer": "answer2"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which one of the following keywords is used for defining the function in the JavaScript ?",
    "answer1": "Void",
    "answer2": "init",
    "answer3": "main",
    "answer4": "function",
    "correctAnswer": "answer4"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript ?",
    "answer1": "getElementById",
    "answer2": "getElementsByClassName()",
    "answer3": "Both A and B",
    "answer4": "None of the above",
    "correctAnswer": "answer3"
  }
]
